{
    "subject": "resource/James_N._Cupp",
    "predicate": "ontology/restingPlace",
    "object": "resource/Manassas,_Virginia",
    "human_readable": "The resting place of James N. Cupp is Manassas, Virginia.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.934286892414093,
            "question": "Is Manassas where James N. Cupp was laid to rest?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8943374752998352,
            "question": "Is Manassas, Virginia the burial site of James N. Cupp?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8509311079978943,
            "question": "In which state is James N. Cupp's resting place located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.782308042049408,
            "question": "Can you tell me the location of James N. Cupp's final resting place?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7801403403282166,
            "question": "To what location is James N. Cupp's resting place linked?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5443129539489746,
            "question": "What city in Virginia is associated with James N. Cupp's burial?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45469850301742554,
            "question": "Where is James N. Cupp buried?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43944087624549866,
            "question": "Where can one find the grave of James N. Cupp?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3928469121456146,
            "question": "What is the name of the city where James N. Cupp is buried?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3470176160335541,
            "question": "What is the name of the city that holds James N. Cupp's burial site?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The resting place of James N. Cupp is Manassas, Virginia.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4144_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the city where James N. Cupp is buried?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4144_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where can one find the grave of James N. Cupp?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4144_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where is James N. Cupp buried?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4144_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4144_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4144_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4144_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4144_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4144_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4144_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4144_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4144_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4144_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4144_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information provided, here's my evaluation:\n\n* **Document 1**: This document contains a brief biography of James Norman Cupp, including his birthdate (March 28, 1921), death date (June 2, 2004), and resting place (Manassas, Virginia).\n* **Query**: The query asks about the resting place of James N. Cupp.\n\nGiven this information, I can confidently say that:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`\n\nThe document supports the triple that the resting place of James N. Cupp is Manassas, Virginia."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe document mentions that Colonel Cupp retired to Manassas, Virginia in 1968 and died on 2 June 2004, supporting the statement about his resting place being in Manassas, Virginia."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}